You just gave everyone 30 minutes.
And I think 30 minutes is enough time for the two dries to harden up.
I was like, "What's hardening?
We need to decide on one person to be the dance leader.
The issue of the lack of a dance leader became clear.
We didn't come to a conclusion in the last meeting, but it seems to be somewhat solidifying among the group.
It's pretty loose.
Nagi would say, "Let's start at this time," or "When you think of what you want to do next, just say so.
I really appreciated that.
We were all aware that Nagi-chan was going to lead the discussion.
We all thought that Nagi-chan would be the one who would be in charge of that kind of thing.
Nagisa Kojima, a person who is always talking, according to the 3rd term students.
With her at the center of the group, the self-directed training also began to change.
She has become more focused.
She is not the type of person who can lead everyone well.
I am not the type of person who can lead everyone well, so I am trying to make everyone feel that it is fun to be active together.
I don't know if I can be called a mood maker.
I don't know if I am a mood maker.
I don't know if I am a mood-maker or not, but I hope I can contribute to the group from that position.
The upcoming presentation of the van will be performed in front of the choreographer, Mr. Takahiro, and the staff, just as at the training camp.
Before the presentation, another big event was coming up for the third-term students.
It is the first meeting with the first and second term students!
I'm so excited to meet my juniors for the first time, and I've been excited about it since this morning.
What do you think?
I'd like to give them a warm welcome.
I'm getting nervous too.
The third term students came here because they love Sakurazaka 46.
My dream is to become a member of Sakurazaka 46 and to work together with my seniors to make the group more exciting!
In my kindergarten graduation album, there was a column for writing my dream for the future, and I wrote "idol" there.
I wondered if I would be able to join the group, but since there are 11 of us, I knew I would not be joining alone, and there are others around me who feel the same way.
I hope that I can be an opportunity for someone to look forward.
I hope I can be a trigger for someone to look forward.
If it weren't for Mr. Sakurazaka, I probably wouldn't be here.
I probably wouldn't have been able to look forward like this.
I don't think I would have been able to look forward like this.
There are many situations in my life where I am glad to have Mr. Sakurazaka.
Mr. Sakurazaka has been a great influence in my life.
At my school, we are required to write a novel.
I wrote a story about love and loneliness.
There was a time when I was thinking about it and I couldn't finish it.
That's when I came across Sakurazaka's accidental answer.
When I saw the expression on Ms. Karin Fujiyoshi's face
I thought that this must be the kind of expression and emotion I wanted to write.
I was able to write the novel.
I was able to finish the novel.
I fell in love with Sakurazaka.
It's like a half-joking story, like I'm going to become an idol.
And my friends were also talking about it.
I've never made such a serious effort to become an idol.
I haven't lived my whole life to be an idol.
I can't sing or dance.
I want to be an idol with steady performance ability, but I haven't caught up yet.
But I haven't caught up yet.
What made me audition?
I watched Ten Yamazaki's broadcast of the joint audition for Sakamichi.
Really?
Yes, and I really liked him.
I didn't know much about what happened after I was assigned to the group.
I liked the songs.
I didn't know much about it at all.
Samidario was on a lot of music shows, you know?
I really liked their music.
I was watching it, and I was like, "What, the girl in the center? And I was like...
I thought, "Is that the one? So I looked it up.
And then I found out that they had figured it out.
I started to know a lot more about it.
So, you know, there are girls who were fans of mine.
So, compared to them, I don't know much about it.
About the Zelkova era...
But, you know, I really like you.
If you have that feeling, you'll be fine.
The camera, the camera...
Oh no!
Sorry.
I'd like to be the kind of person who can create a good atmosphere
I've always loved idols who idolize idols.
But when I met Keyakizaka 46.
I fell in love with it and fell in love with it.
I don't know why I'm so crazy about Sakurazaka.
I don't even know why.
I'm instinctively attracted to it.
I think Sakurazaka has a charm that no one else has.
There's something about Sakurazaka that attracts me in a way that no one else can.
I'm crying a lot right now.
I'm showing my weak side to everyone.
I want to be a strong idol who doesn't show that kind of weakness.
I want to become a strong idol.
You have supported me a lot so far.
If I become an idol, I would like to be able to support others just as you have supported me.
I thought that if I became an idol, I might be able to support someone just as you have supported me in the past.
Miyo Matono is the youngest of the 3rd term students.
She sometimes shows her innocence in her cool atmosphere.
Gafflio boom is so slow.
I want to make marshmallows.
Hey, can't you fly?
I just saw you.
I just caught a glimpse.
Shall we make it?
Let's make some marshmallows.
I don't know if I can put my fingers in it.I don't know if I can put my finger on it.
How long will it take?
Does it have UV?
No UV.
It doesn't burn.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, it won't.
I want to be what the seniors, the third-term students, and the fans need me to be.
I want to be someone who is needed.
I never wanted to be an idol.
Basically, I didn't like school.
I didn't have many friends.
When I heard Ms. Sakurazaka's song
I had many moments when I felt I wasn't alone.
I thought I wanted to join.
I've always wanted to be a member of Keyakizaka since they started.
I thought, "These people are so cool, I want to support them.
Maybe for the first time.
Sakurazaka's lyrics are amazing.
It's like they accompany me in my life.
I'm still not used to it, so I admire them.
I hope I can shine as an idol in my own way.
I've never thought that I wanted to be an idol.
Congratulations!
Congratulations.
You are the 11 members of the third term.
First of all, please introduce yourself one by one.
I am a third-year student in the third term.
I am 20 years old and from Gunma Prefecture.
I am Yumika Ishimori. I look forward to working with you.
Please give me your best regards.
I have loved you for 7 years.
Please take care of me from now on.
I am Riko Endo, a 16-year-old high school sophomore from Saitama Prefecture.
I really admire seniors, and I will do my best to catch up with them. I look forward to working with you.
I am looking forward to working with you.
I would like to work hard so that I don't run behind the group Sakuradoko46 that the seniors have created.
Atoo ně shan
I will do my best to be loved by you all from now on.
I will do my best as a third term student so that everyone will be glad that she is here.
To the fans who love the current Sakurazaka
I will do my best so that the fans who love Sakurazaka now will support Sakurazaka after the third term students join the group.
Thank you very much for your support.
I would like to be someone that everyone can look up to.
I would like to become a person that everyone can look up to, so please take care of me.
Please take care of me.
I will do my best to perform like the seniors.
I look forward to working with you.
I am very happy to join my favorite group in the world.
I love sending concerts and live videos to you.
I will do my best to help you.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
Nice to meet you all, 3rd term students.
Seino!
I am Sakurazaka FONTEN6.
Welcome to Sakurazaka!
We are really looking forward to meeting you 3rd term students.
We were really looking forward to meeting you 3rd term students, and we could feel how hard you all worked to convey your various thoughts and feelings to us.
We are really looking forward to working together as Sakurazaka from now on.
I am really looking forward to working together as Sakurazaka from now on, and I am sure that we will become a better group in the future.
I am really looking forward to working together as Sakurazaka.
I look forward to working with you.
Yes, thank you very much.
I was hoping to be on the same page as you as much as possible, but I became shy on my own. I was shy. I was very shy. I couldn't make eye contact with them, so I kept looking around here. I was looking at my stomach.
I could tell that they applied because they admired and liked Sakurazaka, so I was genuinely happy. I think we will be working with these girls and seeing a new side of Sakurazaka, so I was looking forward to that.
I thought they were all cute, and although many of them were not necessarily 10 years younger than the first group, I could see a sparkle in their eyes when they looked at us, and I really felt their love for us.
I was also very happy to see that. Let's go for it!
Finally, the day of the presentation arrived!
While making final adjustments before the presentation
Mr. Takahiro came to see us in person!
Mr. Takahiro came to see us
ED
I just thought, "I've come to do it now".
But when I put it out at a live performance
I think it's going to be a different impression.
Endo Taniguchi
Nakajima
I can hear you sing, so you're working really hard, right?
So you're all working really hard, and they're like, "Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, there.
When you are in a space like this or in a live space, it's easy to focus on the people who are singing.
It's important to have a singing voice.
The first "hey" is important. You have to say "hey.
This is where you grab it.
A little bit stronger at the back of the song, like a little bit longer or a little bit stronger at the back.
Okay.
Okay! It's getting better!
I want you to bring this energy out as you perform.
It's not a time to see how good you are, it's a time to see how much energy you can generate.
Yes, sir.
Ishimori, you're going through something, right?
But it's good to cry.
If you can cry, it means you are someone who can understand the feelings of those who can cry.
This kind of thing happens a lot.
When you are performing, there are days when something happens or someone is in pain.
I know the members feel like they're going to be hard with me at that time.
To always pull them up on stage.
It's not about being hard together.It's not about being hard together.
Then let's double our power.
Ishimori will be like, "Okay! We can do it.
The important thing is to do the best we can do today.
See, I told you about Monstash.
Don't suddenly tell me I'm not good enough because I'm not where I want to be.
I've said enough, enough already.
Depending on how this BAUM presentation goes.
I'll decide whether or not to make a music video for the third-term students.
There's a lot of pressure on the center.
My name is Nagisa Kojima, Sakurazaka 46 3rd term student. We have been working together for the past month, all 11 of us, to make a bang for the 3rd term students.
We all supported each other when someone was having a hard time at practice or when we were sad.
Today, with the teamwork we have built up so far, the 11 of us will unite our hearts and deliver the best performance we can now.
Please do us all a favor.